[SPEAKER_01]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_00]: So, do you have, do you have a long, I guess not, not up there. See, I was raised in New York, but I guess up there you all don't have too long of a growing season, do you?
[SPEAKER_01]: Um, well, we probably have about three months.
[SPEAKER_00]: This is a transcription of the audio.
[SPEAKER_01]: Ah, thank you.
[SPEAKER_00]: How do you do your own gardening?
[SPEAKER_01]: Mm-hm. We live on a, used to be a farm but we don't farm it. We, but we do have a garden.
[SPEAKER_00]: We live on a used to be a farm but we don't farm it. We're here but we do have a garden.
[SPEAKER_01]: Ah
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, let's see. I put in pepper plants this weekend.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, I wish I could be doing that.
[SPEAKER_00]: I wish I could be doing that. Yeah, I got all my little seedlings coming up in the kitchen and
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay
[SPEAKER_00]: I enjoy tinkering with it, you know. It's pretty hot down here during the summer. We hit, you know, 100, 102 sometimes.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, it's pretty hot down here during the summer. We hit, you know, 100, 102 sometimes.
[SPEAKER_00]: and we don't do too much during the summer as far as tomatoes and stuff. Yeah, almost half of it gets
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, almost have to get started pretty early probably.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_00]: Usually I can put in, oh, probably mid-March I can put anything in the ground, you know, beets and onions and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_01]: you know, beats and onions and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_00]: but then I have to wait for my tomatoes have to go in here in the next couple of weeks
[SPEAKER_01]: Ah!
[SPEAKER_00]: as soon as we're sure we're not going to have another freeze then we'll finish it
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah. You've had more praising this winner or this yeah winner, I think.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, we had a couple of
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes, yes, that's right.
[SPEAKER_00]: just a few, you know, it freezes a little here and there, but
[SPEAKER_01]: But
[SPEAKER_00]: Every once in a while we get a freeze around the middle of April and it's pretty tough.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's pretty tough. Are you do you work or are you retired or
[SPEAKER_00]: No, I work.
[SPEAKER_01]: This is a transcription of the audio.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm only forty years old. I have to work.
[SPEAKER_01]: Uh, my husband's retired, but he's not a gardener. He's been helping me more, but he really isn't, uh,
[SPEAKER_00]: But he's not a card.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm a little crazy about it. Sorry.
[SPEAKER_00]: I I really enjoyed it. It gives me time outdoors. You know, I'm a golfer, but
[SPEAKER_01]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_00]: It gives me time outdoors and time around my house.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, um, the
[SPEAKER_00]: I've burned my grass off here in the last couple of days.
[SPEAKER_01]: Ah, ah.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm getting ready to start for the spring season and seeing if I can grow me another nice lawn. I usually have a pretty nice lawn. It's a lot of work.
[SPEAKER_01]: Um.