[SPEAKER_00]: In this scenario, the great managers demonstrated GC value of being a customer, usual customer observation. Uh, how the customer, how the great managers shown that quantity. So, uh, customer has valued the positive time available with the customer.
[SPEAKER_00]: Instead of showing a negative facial expressions or body language, he has remained calm enough to handle the customer's adamant nature. He has also shown the quality of GC value of being uh, to show respect. So instead of arguing with the customers in absence of sharing the required informations, uh the customer
[SPEAKER_00]: The credit managers persuade the customer, the client to in the humblest manner to share the required information and the last what did they what G.C. managers paid many demonstrators of corruption. Good evening ma'am. My name is Vishal and I'm from the credit system and World Bank capital.
[SPEAKER_01]: Uh, we haven't received no loan application of four and a half CRP box. So, uh, to start with, can you just take us through your end-time business, uh, like since you work, what you're that inclined since when you're at when you
[SPEAKER_02]: I've already shared you all my documents. I'm sure you've already done your research because everything's available on topic at home.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm answering your questions through your AI proposals to the kind of advice which you have provided for me. So the agenda of this meeting is to get some insights from you and to understand from them what exactly we are doing in this business because this is very crucial for us, clearly from a writing perspective.
[SPEAKER_02]: What do you exactly want?
[SPEAKER_01]: Just um briefly guiding on and so uh so I uh suppose you are into uh and so you are you be into electronic goods and just wanted to understand whether you are into manufacturing or whether you are into trading
[SPEAKER_02]: I've already provided you my financials. All of this is very clearly stated in there. I think you'll not control.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay. And then who are your suppliers basically and to whom do you supply? So we have branches, partners, we are all we will be focusing on specific regions.
[SPEAKER_02]: How is this relevant? I mean nobody's ever asked me who my suppliers are. I've been taking a lot of borrowings from the industry, but this is just not relevant. I'll opt for stake because I really have a lot of meetings scheduled up.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, so that's okay, ma'am. Like, uh, like we will connect with your CEO for uh regarding on these points. However, due to short of time when you are having back to media, so we will stick to only few open points on which we require the application to go ahead with your proposal. That's mainly because this could be a very important thing which we would need uh for the decision of your proposal.
[SPEAKER_01]: On this class. Yeah. So I mean the first point there were deep margins so in financial your your gross margin were in the range of 5.5%, which which moved down to 3, 3.5% in the in the in this financial year. But it took so what exactly was the reason of this?
[SPEAKER_02]: This is a test.
[SPEAKER_02]: So this was due to COVID. Uh, there was a drop in all industries were affected. Obviously, I'm sure you're aware of this. So that's why my margins had dropped. Uh, now there's a lot of competition that's being faced in the area that we, you know, operated. So that's the reason uh there's a drop in margin. However, post-COVID, uh the margins have picked up and we have also expanded our, like to expand our online platforms. So the margins are up.
[SPEAKER_01]: Popeye, for a pocket.
[SPEAKER_01]: And um we have taken a recent loan on seven and a half year from Exway Bank Limited and uh if I see your borrowing patterns of over the last 12 months we have taken uh we have taken loans of between 25 to 30 year which includes working capital loan also and various term loans also. So uh wanted to know where exactly we had used this uh early to um business expansion in work because we can see multiple borrowings over the last
[SPEAKER_02]: So I have found it with the exam breakup, but um overall we have diverted a few funds towards business expansion. We're opening a couple of branches. We're exploring online modes for the business and a portion of it is also being used for working.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay, okay, okay. And there were a few launches that also, so it seems like you might be specifically seeing some spyware problems. Yeah, so what exactly started? Can you just throw some
[SPEAKER_02]: Uh, it's just to explore the online worlds. There's nothing to share about it now because it's in a nascent state.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay, okay, okay. I understand, guys. So, uh, so man, uh, you are looking for a loan amount of uh, four and a half crore, right? To fill out.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's already mentioned on the application.
[SPEAKER_01]: We are setting up a check. So, uh, what will be the end use of our files? I will now unwind with the image.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's all about my phone working gap. If I follow the online mode that I want to start, it's all about.
[SPEAKER_01]: Online order about start. So basically to purchase some stocks and one basically we are starting on in doing this for the we don't want stock.
[SPEAKER_02]: How?
[SPEAKER_01]: that okay
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm just going to
[SPEAKER_01]: I am a student, I am a new family member.
[SPEAKER_02]: How's that relevant to your funding beyond my business?
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm not in any support or anything. Any work else from your family is involved in this or you are managing that, that's all.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, this is my own, but myself and my
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay. Okay. And this is a fabric business called
[SPEAKER_02]: The break is over because this was my father, but now he's retired. So my husband and I are coming.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay, okay. Okay, ma'am. So thank you so much for your time and we would like to connect with you again in case we need any further clarification. Uh, so as of now there were some documents which we needed uh uh to get this uh program started. So uh from this can we connect with your CEO directly?
[SPEAKER_02]: They will be the best to help you. I am not able to connect my account with my account or my CI.
[SPEAKER_00]: I will be able to. I will solve this. Thank you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks.
[SPEAKER_01]: Um.
[SPEAKER_00]: So as we seen in the scenario where the TD was conducted by a trade wise. So here the here the in this scenario the trade wise is demonstrated in multiple quantities keeping in mind the GC values. So one of the multiple quantities in the state
[SPEAKER_00]: So first one is uh prior to conducting the PD, the credit manager was thorough and have thorough understanding of the business. He has asked relevant questions with regards to financials and the banking. Uh second, the questions asked were relevant enough, were appropriate enough to understand the creditors' state of affairs, his financial standing as on date. Uh
[SPEAKER_00]: After assessing the adamant nature of the customer, the trade manager's smartness twisted his questions to gain the customer's confidence. See, we can clearly see how the customer has changed his response from not being supportive, not being responsible to be a piece providing the required assistance when he assessed that the trade manager has smartly analyzed his financials and he has came very prepared prior to conducting the P&L. So this was the quality what trade managers demonstrated at individual level.